(node:37792) ExperimentalWarning: SQLite is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ actual settings-selected owners certify exact A B A B with full model and tokenizer hashes (2.3578ms)
✔ missing current-run composition remains incomplete (0.1983ms)
✔ extra owner composition is rejected rather than compressed (0.8597ms)
✔ wrong owner order, path, model hash, and tokenizer hash are each rejected (0.3483ms)
✔ truncated hashes, relative paths, and malformed JSON cannot certify owner identity (0.5333ms)
✔ legacy truncated consumer records remain rejected beside valid current identities (0.1734ms)
(node:27388) ExperimentalWarning: SQLite is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ availability before reload does not certify recovery (0.917ms)
✔ index-starting samples contribute to the API outage window (0.8554ms)
✔ only a matching vector response after the last refusal certifies recovery (0.1723ms)
✔ a clean in-place transition reports the restart outage separately and passes D1-14 (0.5593ms)
✔ a vector refusal away from RELOADING violates the structural window (0.209ms)
✔ hybrid failing inside the refusal window violates keyword continuity (0.0975ms)
✔ samples without a hybrid probe cannot certify keyword continuity (0.1293ms)
(node:11780) ExperimentalWarning: SQLite is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ terminal success and IDLE do not settle a promoted predecessor (0.4894ms)
✔ only the exact target with no candidate and no predecessor is settled (0.1293ms)
✔ settlement preserves every field for strict same-key replay comparison (0.6511ms)
✔ fixture refuses a spoofed WDAG user before creating the supplied work path (73.2661ms)
✔ GenerateOnly stages a closed WSB contract and preserves source AST validity (1473.941ms)
(node:21752) ExperimentalWarning: SQLite is an experimental feature and might change at any time
(Use `node --trace-warnings ...` to show where the warning was created)
✔ BESIDE admits corpus, holds A, rejects stale publication, and replays refusal (237.0952ms)
✔ IN_PLACE admits corpus, holds A, rejects stale publication, and replays refusal (218.8661ms)
✔ delayed retry rejects reapplyOldKey (95.4758ms)
✔ delayed retry rejects corruptReplay (94.3511ms)
✔ delayed retry rejects acceptStaleWitness (127.7468ms)
✔ model-query timeout preserves HTTP, result count, and missing trace evidence (3.0737ms)
ℹ tests 24
ℹ suites 0
ℹ pass 24
ℹ fail 0
ℹ cancelled 0
ℹ skipped 0
ℹ todo 0
ℹ duration_ms 1627.3416
